 question 1: -Given a number, find the next smallest palindrome larger than the number. Give an 
 optimized solution rather than a brute force algorithm.
 Few examples

 Input Number Output - The next smallest palindrome
 125      131
 250      252
 123      131
 397      404
 4512     4554 
 1234     1331 
 1997     2002

Write the below function

int nextPalindrome(int input){
}


 Question 2: - ATM Dispenser Simulator

  Design a function that simulates an ATM machine dispensing money. The ATM contains 
  various denominations of bills, and a customer requests a specific withdrawal amount. the 
  function should determine whether the ATM can fulfil the request based on the available
  notes and their quantities. 

  Input:

 withdrawal_amount (positive integer): the amount of money the customer wants to 
 withdraw.

 atm_notes (data structure): A data structure representing the available denominations (keys) 
 and their corresponding quantities (values) in the ATM. This data structure can he a 
 HashMap (Java)

 programming language.

 Example:


 withdrawal amount = 270

 atm_notes =
 100: 5, # 5 notes of $100 denomination
 50:3,#3 notes of $50 denomination
 20:2,#2 notes of $20 denomination
 10:1 #1 note of $10 denomination

}


Output:


  • Return a data structure indicating the number of notes dispensed from each 
    denomination (if successful). This data structure should mirror the format used for

    atm_notes.

  • For 270 withdrawal ATM can dispense below notes.

    atm_notes =

     100: 2, # 2 notes of $100 denomination
    50: 1, # 1 note of $50 denomination 
    20: 1, # 1 note of $20 denomination




        Question 3:-     You have to distribute N coconuts equally among some elephants according to the following 

                        conditions:

                             •     You can choose the number of elephants that receive coconuts.
                             •      Each elephant should get more than one coconut.
                             •       One elephant cannot receive all the coconuts.
                             •      All the N coconuts must be distributed.                                                                                                                                                                              1. 4.- '4;
                             •      Each elephant can only receive full coconuts. You can't distribute half 
                                   coconut.

                    Write a program to determine whether the coconuts can be equally distributed among the 
                    elephants. There will be bonus marks for optimizing the solution.

                                                                                               Output
                              Input

                      N coconuts to be distributed.                                            Return true or false depending upon the result.

                       Examples
                                                                                                                        
                        N = 2

                 2 coconuts cannot be distributed among group of any size. suppose we take a group of size 1
                  then one elephant takes all the coconuts. If we take a group of size 2 each elephant will only 
                  1 coconut which violates the rule of distribution

               N 15 =                                                      
              15 coconut can be equally  distributed among 3 elephants each one getting 5 coconuts.


               static boolean distribute(int N) 


                                                                                                                                                           Scanned with OKEN Scanner

        In a company, each employee has a direct manager (except the CEO) and zero or more direct
        reporters. Au employee with at least one reportee is called a manager. The company has a 
        CEO, who is the only employee with no manager.

       The relationship between each employee and their manager is represented by a table with two 

       columns: 'Employee' and 'Manager', where each row represents an employee and their direct 
       manager. You can assume a data structure to hold the employee — manager relationship 
       which help you print the required output.


      Write a function print() where:

         •  The function should print the names of all employees in the company grouped by 
            their level in the hierarchy.

        •  The CEO is at level 1, employees who directly report to the CEO are at level 2, 
           employees who directly report to level 2 employees are at level 3, and so on.
        •
    In this example:                                              
  Employee   Manager 
  Bob       Alice
  Charlie     Alice 
  David      Alice 
  Eve        Bob 
  Frank       Bob
  Grace       Bob
  Helen     Charlie
  Irene     Charlie 
  Jack      Charlie 
  Karen      David 
  Larry     David 
  Mike      David 
  Nancy        Eve 
  Oscar      Frank 
  Peter      Grace 
  Quinn      Helen 
  Rachel      Irene
  Sam        Jack 
  Tim        Karen
  Uma        Larry

 •  Alice is the CEO.  
•  Bob, Charlie and David report directly to Alice. 
 Eve, Frank and Grace report to Bob; Helen, Irene and Jack
 report to Charlie; Karen Larry and Mike report to David.
Nancy reports to Eve; Oscar reports to Frank; Peter reports 
to Grace; Quinn reports to Helen; Rachel reports to Irene;
Sam reports to Jack; Tim reports to Karen; Uma reports to 
 Larry. 


  Output 
Level 1: Alice  
 Level 2: Bob Charlie David 
 Level 3: Eve Frank Grace Helen Irene Jack Karen Larry Mike
 Level 4: Nancy Oscar Peter Quinn Rachel Sam Tim Uma 

This is a programming/coding problem not a SQL problem.                                                                



                                                   

  You have to load some order data in an application. The data object Order contains two 
  attributes order-Id and entry time, for example


   Order-Time of entry
      Id

    0124 10:15

    0345 9:15

    0873 13:30

   0314  7:30


 We will load millions of Order objects in memory. We have sufficient ram and memory 
 requirements is not a constraint.

 After loading the Order objects in a collection we want to perform searches on the loaded 
 data. Given a start and end time, the application should be able to find all
 orders entered during the time period very efficiently.

   1. Which collection or data structure will you use to load the data so that it helps in 
      search operation? You just need to decide the collection or data structure; it can be 
      assumed the code for loading objects into the desired collection is already written and
      does not need to be implemented.
   2. Implement an efficient search method as follows
           public Collection<Order> search (Time startTime, Time endTime){....}
   3. What is the time complexity of your search method implementation? Use Big 0
     notation.



Write code for
public Collection<Order> search (Time startTime, Time endTime){


}




=====================================================================
you are tasked with  designing a database schema for a car rental management system. 
the system needs to manage information about cars,customers,rental transactions, and car
maintenancec records. your objective is to define the necessary tables, primary keys, foreign key
relationships and answer for few queries.

business requirements:-

1- the car rental company has many cars
2-  each car can be rented multiple times
3-  the company has many customers
4- customers can rent multiples cars
5- each rental transaction should record the date when the car was rented and the
data when it was returned.
6- each car can have multiple maintenance records.
7- maintenance records should include the date of maintenance and details of the
maintenance performed.

Queries

1- find all customers who have not rented any cars, along with their names
and email addresses.
2- find the total number of rentals for each car, along with the car make,
model and year.
3- find the names of customers who have rented more than three different cars.


task :-
1-define the normalized tables and their columns based on the business requirements.
2- specify the primary and forrign key relationships
3- answer the queries provided

https://chatgpt.com/c/9e25527d-873a-4bc3-a753-b44b900c3023




















